jimmychoo.com 2013-05-26

# Legal Terms | Jimmy Choo

**USE OF SITE**

Use of this Site, which is owned by J. Choo Limited (JCL) of 10 Howick Place, London, SW1P 1GW United Kingdom (Company Registered Number: 3185783) (VAT Number: GB 849150905), is subject to the following legal terms. 

Copyright and all other intellectual property rights in both the content of this Site owned by JCL and licensed to JIMMY CHOO (OS) Limited. Copyright © 2006 J. Choo Limited. Except as expressly set out below, all rights reserved. 

Content included in the Site may be accessed by you for your own internal non commercial use only. You may not copy, perform, publish, modify, transfer, create derivative works from, commercially exploit or otherwise use in whole or part any content, software, products or services obtained from this Site. 

You may not delete or alter in any way any copyright, trade mark, intellectual property or other legal notices from any part of this Site. 

You will keep any password assigned to you which permits access to this Site or any part of this Site strictly confidential and not divulge it to any other person. Unauthorised use of this Site, including, but not limited to, unauthorised entry into it, misuse of passwords or misuse of any other information, is strictly prohibited. 

You may not use this Site in any manner that could damage, disable, overburden, or impair this Site or interfere with any other party's access to and/or use of this Site. 

You may not attempt to gain unauthorised access to this Site, computer systems or networks connected to this Site, through hacking, password mining or any other means. You must not use these facilities to commit or encourage a criminal offence, to insert, transmit or distribute viruses or corrupt data or to send any unsolicited advertisement or other promotional material (that is, "spam"). 

You agree that you will not engage in any activities related to this Site that are contrary to applicable laws or regulations. You may not use this Site for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these legal terms. 

Unless authorised in writing by JCL, JCL expressly prohibits linking of any part of this Site to or from any other Sites (including so-called "deep-linking"). 

You are prohibited from using any marks for any purpose including, but not limited to use as metatags on other pages or Sites on the World Wide Web. 

JCL may terminate your access and use of any part of this Site at any time without notice if you are in breach of any of the terms of these legal terms. 

**RETURNS**

All returns for any particular order need to be returned in one shipment. Any subsequent returns from the same order may incur additional shipping costs. The RMA number should be written on your original invoice and on the return-shipping label (DHL Air waybill slip). We request that returns are shipped through our shipping partner DHL or, for London Premier orders our London courier service. JCL is not liable for any returned goods which are not returned in this way. The return address is stated on the pre-printed shipping label supplied with your goods. Failure to obtain an RMA or return goods using neither DHL nor our London Premier courier service does not affect your statutory rights. 

JCL will not accept returns for any non-faulty items that have been worn and tags removed. Upon receipt of an order, if any item has been received with no tags, customer should notify us (by phone or email) on the same day if they wish to return. We strongly advise all customers to check products thoroughly upon delivery before removing any attached tags and before disposing of any original packaging. 

Please be aware that shoes must be returned with their original designer packaging. Shoes returned without their original boxes will not be accepted. 

Please be aware that international customs duties and sales taxes are NOT refunded for shipments outside the European Community (EU). 

Should you wish to exchange an item for an alternative size, please email us when you request your RMA number and we will reserve it for you if the item is in stock. As soon as we receive your return, we will dispatch your new size to you after the goods have undergone a quality control check. 

If you are located outside the EU you will be required to pay additional taxes and duties on the replacement item. 

Please be aware that we are unable to exchange an item for an alternative colour or style, subject to availability. 

**REPAIRS**

JCL will not accept claims for goods which have been repaired or altered in anyway by anyone other than JCL. Furthermore, JCL strongly discourages the addition of rubber protective soles onto JCL products. For details on how to repair your JIMMY CHOOs please contact customer care. 

**DISCLAIMER**

The content included in this Site is provided on an "as is" basis. JCL does not give any other warranty, express or implied, or make any representation including without limitation that the content included in this Site is complete or accurate or up to date. JCL reserves the right in its sole discretion and without any obligation or notice requirement to change, alter or edit content included in this Site. 

JCL will not be liable for any damages (including without limitation for loss of profits, loss of business or of anticipated savings, loss of goodwill, loss of reputation, loss or corruption of data or for any type of special, indirect, incidental or consequential loss or damage) whether arising out of your use or delay or inability to use this Site or its content whether arising in contract, tort (including negligence) or otherwise except in the case of fraud or death or personal injury caused by JCL's negligence. 

JCL does not take responsibility for any event which is outside its reasonable control nor for any consequential loss arising from such an event. 

You agree that JCL may use personal information provided by you in order to conduct appropriate anti fraud checks. Personal information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information. For more information please refer to our Privacy Policy. 

From time to time, JCL may change, alter or modify these legal terms. Any changes to these legal terms will be posted on this Site and any use by you of this Site after any such changes have been posted shall be deemed to indicate your agreement to the modified legal terms, but will not affect any orders already placed by you. If you do not agree to the modified legal terms, you should cease use of this Site. 

**LEGAL GOVERNANCE**

These legal terms shall be governed by and interpreted in accordance with English law and the courts of England shall have non-exclusive jurisdiction to hear all disputes arising in connection with these conditions. 

* * *

**PRIVACY POLICY**

This privacy statement was last updated on 20th April 2012. 

We respect your privacy and understand the importance of protecting your personally identifiable information. This privacy statement identifies and describes the types of personally identifiable information we may collect from you when you visit the JIMMY CHOO website , how we use this information, when we share this information with third parties, and how we protect this information. By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by JIMMY CHOO. 

We reserve the right to modify, alter, or otherwise update this statement at any time, and we encourage you to check back periodically so that you are always aware of the most current policies and practices that JIMMY CHOO has in place to protect your personally identifiable information. Please contact our customer care team at [customercare@jimmychooonline.com](mailto:customercare@jimmychooonline.com) if you have any questions about our privacy statement. 

**WHAT INFORMATION DOES JIMMY CHOO GATHER ABOUT YOU?**

1\. Personally Identifiable Information: We may collect personally identifiable information from you, including your name, email address, physical address, phone number, certain payment card information, gender, and birthdate when you order JIMMY CHOO items through our website; purchase our products in our retail stores; save your information with us online; sign up to receive promotional materials via mail or email; or participate in a contest, promotion or survey. Some of the personally identifiable information we collect from you, including your name, address, phone number, email address, and certain payment card information, is required in order to process your online purchases, respond to your requests, and contact you about your online purchases, if necessary. 

2\. Automated Information: We also collect non-personally identifiable information when you interact with our website and respond to our electronic communications and advertisements, which enables us to enhance your shopping experience by tailoring information to fit your personal preferences. Examples of non-personally identifiable information that we may collect include the date and time of your visit, your originating IP address, the web pages and images that you request, your purchases, cookies, and web beacons. 

**COOKIES**

A cookie is a small amount of data sent from our server and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

Cookies that are strictly necessary for the operation of the Website: Some of the cookies we use are essential for parts of the Website to operate and are already set. These are strictly necessary for the sale of products requested by you and without them the Website cannot operate as intended. 

**Cookie Name**

| 

**Originating Page**

| 

**Purpose**

| 

**Expiry**  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
locn

| 

All

| 

Collecting region code and setting user region

| 

Never  
  
lang

| 

All

| 

Collecting language code and setting display language

| 

Never  
  
RFID

| 

Add to basket/log in

| 

User reference id + verification hash collected, for the purposes of session control.

| 

Never  
  
SID

| 

First page visited

| 

Collects session ID for the purposes of session control.

| 

Never  
  
RVI

| 

Viewing items

| 

Collects list of recently viewed items for the purposes of displaying "recently viewed items" panel.

| 

One week  
  
vbmprods

| 

Viewing items

| 

Collects list of recently viewed items for the purposes of displaying "recommended items" panel.

| 

One week  
  
vbmtracker

| 

Viewing items

| 

Collects recommended items tracking code for the purposes of building "recommended items" data.

| 

One week  
  
newCurr

| 

Viewing currency exchange rates

| 

Collects data on currency to rate against in order to provide an exchange rate

| 

One week  
  
referid

| 

First page visited

| 

Referral data to track sites that link to Venda

| 

2 days  
  
httprefer

| 

First page visited

| 

Referral data to track sites that link to Venda

| 

2 days  
  
Setview 

| 

Product list/ search list page

| 

Keeps user's preference for the product information display page.

| 

1 week  
  
setViewPerPage 

| 

Product list/ search list page

| 

Keeps user's preference for the number of products to view per page.

| 

1 week  
  
RSI

| 

Search

| 

Keeps last 3 keyword searches for the purpose of displaying the last 3 key words so users can quickly go back to them.

| 

1 day  
  
Tracking tags

| 

Various

| 

Analytical services

| 

Not disclosed  
  
Quench

| 

All

| 

First

| 

Managing performance on the Venda platform  
  
**Other uses of cookies (where you have consented to such use):**

Where you consent to us doing so, we also use cookies and other such devices to compile anonymous, aggregated statistics that allow us to understand how users use our Website and to help us improve the structure of our Website (we cannot identify you personally in this way). We use cookies and other such devices to allow us to understand who has seen which pages and advertisements on the Website, to determine how frequently particular such pages and advertisements are visited, to determine the most popular areas of the Website and generally in order to monitor usage of the Website. 

Where you consent to us doing so, we may also use cookies and other such devices to:   
• to allow you to carry information across pages of our Website and avoid having to re-enter information; 

• within registration to allow you to access stored information; 

• to help us recognise you as a unique visitor when you return to our Website and to allow us to tailor content or advertisements to match your preferred interests or to avoid showing you the same adverts repeatedly; 

• speed up searches; and/or 

• within research surveys to ensure you are not invited to complete a questionnaire too often or after you have already done so. 

**Browser settings:**

Most internet browsers are automatically set up to accept cookies, but you can set your browser to refuse a cookie or ask your browser to show you where a cookie has been set up. Certain services are only activated by the presence of a cookie and, if you choose to refuse cookies, particular features of this Website may not be available to you. 

Find out how to disable/enable cookies by clicking on the “Manage Cookies” section of the Interactive Advertising Bureau UK website on the following link [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

We may use Adobe Flash Player to display video or image content. It may not possible to block or restrict flash cookies using your browser settings. However information on how to control flash playerprivacy and security settings is available from the Adobe website at: <http://www.adobe.com/products/flashplayer/security>

**HOW DOES JIMMY CHOO USE YOUR INFORMATION?**

We may use information you provide to us for a variety of purposes, including to process purchases, refunds, exchanges, and other transactions; to contact you about questions or communications regarding your order; to respond to your customer service inquiries; to contact you about new products, services, special events and promotions, unless you have elected otherwise in accordance with the “How Can You Access or Change Your Information?” section of this privacy statement ; to help us learn about your shopping preferences; to help us improve our website, retail stores, products and services; and to enhance your shopping experience. We may combine any information collected about you in our retail stores with the information collected through our website in order to enhance and personalize your shopping experience, and for promotional purposes. 

**DOES JIMMY CHOO SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH OTHERS?**

Except as described in this privacy statement, we do not sell, share or distribute your personally identifiable information to third parties. 

All personally identifiable information and non-personally identifiable information we collect about you may be shared with our affiliates and subsidiaries. 

We may also share personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable information about you with unaffiliated third parties that collect, manage, analyse or maintain data on our behalf, including website hosting service providers, payment processors, freight forwarders, carriers, companies that conduct or manage our marketing and promotional campaigns, and other third parties that perform services on our behalf (e.g., sending promotions and other communications and conducting contests and surveys).Such third parties may operate outside of the European Economic Area (“EEA”). 

We may also share your information with third parties when we believe such disclosure is required to (i) comply with laws, regulations and/or government policies; (ii) comply with court orders, legal processes, or government enforcement actions; (iii) establish or exercise our legal rights, protect our rights and interests, or defend against legal claims; or (iv) detect, investigate, prevent, or take action with respect to illegal activities, suspected fraud or misconduct, securities or technical issues, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations of our terms of use or privacy policies. 

In the event that we, or any of our affiliates or subsidiaries, are involved in a business transaction such as a merger, an acquisition, or any form of sale of all or a portion of our stock or assets, we may transfer your personally identifiable information to the buyer. 

**HOW CAN YOU ACCESS OR CHANGE YOUR INFORMATION?**

You may access, review and edit the personally identifiable information that you provide to us online. To edit this information, simply sign in to your account on the JIMMY CHOO website using your email address and password, click “My JIMMY CHOO,” and click the appropriate edit option under “Account Details.” 

You can also ask us to update your personally identifiable information or communication preferences by contacting us using the information provided in the “Contact Information” section of this privacy statement. Please note that any request to update your information may take up to 10 business days to process and that you may continue to receive communications from JIMMY CHOO using the previously provided information until your request becomes effective. 

**HOW DOES JIMMY CHOO PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?**

We strive to provide you with a safe, secure shopping experience. To achieve this goal, we have in place certain physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial safeguards to protect the security and privacy of your personally identifiable information. Since the security of any data transmission over the internet cannot be unconditionally guaranteed, any information that you transmit to us is at your own risk. The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the EEA. 

Orders placed online are processed through a third party vendor that uses Secure Socket Layer (“SSL”) technology to protect your personally identifiable information. SSL encrypts your order information, including your name, address, and payment card number before it is transmitted online. 

We also protect your personally identifiable information by requiring you to provide a valid email address and a personal password when you create an account using the JIMMY CHOO website. To protect your personally identifiable information, we strongly encourage you to maintain the secrecy of the password to your JIMMY CHOO account. 

**DOES JIMMY CHOO COLLECT INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13?**

The JIMMY CHOO website is intended for general audiences and is not targeted to or intended for use by children. We do not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If we become aware that a child under the age of thirteen has submitted personally identifiable information through the JIMMY CHOO website without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove such information from our files. 

**LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES**

While using this website, you may be linked or directed to other websites hosted by third parties. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the privacy practices and policies of such third parties or the content of these third party websites. This privacy statement does not describe the information collection and disclosure practices of such third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and statements of such third parties. 

**CONTACT INFORMATION**

We are very sensitive to your privacy concerns and are committed to providing you with a safe, secure web experience. For questions or comments regarding this privacy statement, please contact customer care team at [customercare@jimmychooonline.com](mailto:customercare@jimmychooonline.com). 

* * *

The site is Powered By [](http://www.venda.com/) ([www.venda.com](http://www.venda.com/)) of 101 St Martins Lane, London, WC2N 4AZ, United Kingdom. A global leader in eCommerce solutions.
